// let spanishColumn = document.querySelectorAll('tr td:nth-of-type(2)')
// let englishColumn = document.querySelectorAll('tr td:nth-of-type(3)')

// let finalSpanishWords = [...spanishColumn].map(item => item.innerText).slice(1)
// let finalEnglishWords = [...englishColumn].map(item => item.innerText).slice(1)

// let data = []

// finalSpanishWords.forEach((key,i) => {
// let info = {}
// info.question = finalSpanishWords[i];
// info.answer = finalEnglishWords[i];
// data.push(info);
// })

// copy(data)

let data = [
    {
        "question": "como",
        "answer": "as"
    },
    {
        "question": "I",
        "answer": "I"
    },
    {
        "question": "su",
        "answer": "his"
    },
    {
        "question": "que",
        "answer": "that"
    },
    {
        "question": "él",
        "answer": "he"
    },
    {
        "question": "era",
        "answer": "was"
    },
    {
        "question": "para",
        "answer": "for"
    },
    {
        "question": "en",
        "answer": "on"
    },
    {
        "question": "son",
        "answer": "are"
    },
    {
        "question": "con",
        "answer": "with"
    },
    {
        "question": "ellos",
        "answer": "they"
    },
    {
        "question": "ser",
        "answer": "be"
    },
    {
        "question": "en",
        "answer": "at"
    },
    {
        "question": "uno",
        "answer": "one"
    },
    {
        "question": "tener",
        "answer": "have"
    },
    {
        "question": "este",
        "answer": "this"
    },
    {
        "question": "desde",
        "answer": "from"
    },
    {
        "question": "por",
        "answer": "by"
    },
    {
        "question": "caliente",
        "answer": "hot"
    },
    {
        "question": "palabra",
        "answer": "word"
    },
    {
        "question": "pero",
        "answer": "but"
    },
    {
        "question": "qué",
        "answer": "what"
    },
    {
        "question": "algunos",
        "answer": "some"
    },
    {
        "question": "es",
        "answer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "lo",
        "answer": "it"
    },
    {
        "question": "usted",
        "answer": "you"
    },
    {
        "question": "o",
        "answer": "or"
    },
    {
        "question": "tenido",
        "answer": "had"
    },
    {
        "question": "la",
        "answer": "the"
    },
    {
        "question": "de",
        "answer": "of"
    },
    {
        "question": "a",
        "answer": "to"
    },
    {
        "question": "y",
        "answer": "and"
    },
    {
        "question": "un",
        "answer": "a"
    },
    {
        "question": "en",
        "answer": "in"
    },
    {
        "question": "nos",
        "answer": "we"
    },
    {
        "question": "lata",
        "answer": "can"
    },
    {
        "question": "fuera",
        "answer": "out"
    },
    {
        "question": "otros",
        "answer": "other"
    },
    {
        "question": "eran",
        "answer": "were"
    },
    {
        "question": "que",
        "answer": "which"
    },
    {
        "question": "hacer",
        "answer": "do"
    },
    {
        "question": "su",
        "answer": "their"
    },
    {
        "question": "tiempo",
        "answer": "time"
    },
    {
        "question": "si",
        "answer": "if"
    },
    {
        "question": "lo hará",
        "answer": "will"
    },
    {
        "question": "cómo",
        "answer": "how"
    },
    {
        "question": "dicho",
        "answer": "said"
    },
    {
        "question": "un",
        "answer": "an"
    },
    {
        "question": "cada",
        "answer": "each"
    },
    {
        "question": "decir",
        "answer": "tell"
    },
    {
        "question": "hace",
        "answer": "does"
    },
    {
        "question": "conjunto",
        "answer": "set"
    },
    {
        "question": "tres",
        "answer": "three"
    },
    {
        "question": "querer",
        "answer": "want"
    },
    {
        "question": "aire",
        "answer": "air"
    },
    {
        "question": "así",
        "answer": "well"
    },
    {
        "question": "también",
        "answer": "also"
    },
    {
        "question": "jugar",
        "answer": "play"
    },
    {
        "question": "pequeño",
        "answer": "small"
    },
    {
        "question": "fin",
        "answer": "end"
    },
    {
        "question": "poner",
        "answer": "put"
    },
    {
        "question": "casa",
        "answer": "home"
    },
    {
        "question": "leer",
        "answer": "read"
    },
    {
        "question": "mano",
        "answer": "hand"
    },
    {
        "question": "puerto",
        "answer": "port"
    },
    {
        "question": "grande",
        "answer": "large"
    },
    {
        "question": "deletrear",
        "answer": "spell"
    },
    {
        "question": "añadir",
        "answer": "add"
    },
    {
        "question": "incluso",
        "answer": "even"
    },
    {
        "question": "tierra",
        "answer": "land"
    },
    {
        "question": "aquí",
        "answer": "here"
    },
    {
        "question": "debe",
        "answer": "must"
    },
    {
        "question": "grande",
        "answer": "big"
    },
    {
        "question": "alto",
        "answer": "high"
    },
    {
        "question": "tal",
        "answer": "such"
    },
    {
        "question": "siga",
        "answer": "follow"
    },
    {
        "question": "acto",
        "answer": "act"
    },
    {
        "question": "por qué",
        "answer": "why"
    },
    {
        "question": "preguntar",
        "answer": "ask"
    },
    {
        "question": "hombres",
        "answer": "men"
    },
    {
        "question": "cambio",
        "answer": "change"
    },
    {
        "question": "se fue",
        "answer": "went"
    },
    {
        "question": "luz",
        "answer": "light"
    },
    {
        "question": "tipo",
        "answer": "kind"
    },
    {
        "question": "fuera",
        "answer": "off"
    },
    {
        "question": "necesitará",
        "answer": "need"
    },
    {
        "question": "casa",
        "answer": "house"
    },
    {
        "question": "imagen",
        "answer": "picture"
    },
    {
        "question": "tratar",
        "answer": "try"
    },
    {
        "question": "nosotros",
        "answer": "us"
    },
    {
        "question": "de nuevo",
        "answer": "again"
    },
    {
        "question": "animal",
        "answer": "animal"
    },
    {
        "question": "punto",
        "answer": "point"
    },
    {
        "question": "madre",
        "answer": "mother"
    },
    {
        "question": "mundo",
        "answer": "world"
    },
    {
        "question": "cerca",
        "answer": "near"
    },
    {
        "question": "construir",
        "answer": "build"
    },
    {
        "question": "auto",
        "answer": "self"
    },
    {
        "question": "tierra",
        "answer": "earth"
    },
    {
        "question": "padre",
        "answer": "father"
    },
    {
        "question": "cualquier",
        "answer": "any"
    },
    {
        "question": "nuevo",
        "answer": "new"
    },
    {
        "question": "trabajo",
        "answer": "work"
    },
    {
        "question": "parte",
        "answer": "part"
    },
    {
        "question": "tomar",
        "answer": "take"
    },
    {
        "question": "conseguir",
        "answer": "get"
    },
    {
        "question": "lugar",
        "answer": "place"
    },
    {
        "question": "hecho",
        "answer": "made"
    },
    {
        "question": "vivir",
        "answer": "live"
    },
    {
        "question": "donde",
        "answer": "where"
    },
    {
        "question": "después",
        "answer": "after"
    },
    {
        "question": "espalda",
        "answer": "back"
    },
    {
        "question": "poco",
        "answer": "little"
    },
    {
        "question": "sólo",
        "answer": "only"
    },
    {
        "question": "ronda",
        "answer": "round"
    },
    {
        "question": "hombre",
        "answer": "man"
    },
    {
        "question": "años",
        "answer": "year"
    },
    {
        "question": "vino",
        "answer": "came"
    },
    {
        "question": "show",
        "answer": "show"
    },
    {
        "question": "cada",
        "answer": "every"
    },
    {
        "question": "buena",
        "answer": "good"
    },
    {
        "question": "me",
        "answer": "me"
    },
    {
        "question": "dar",
        "answer": "give"
    },
    {
        "question": "nuestro",
        "answer": "our"
    },
    {
        "question": "bajo",
        "answer": "under"
    },
    {
        "question": "nombre",
        "answer": "name"
    },
    {
        "question": "muy",
        "answer": "very"
    },
    {
        "question": "a través de",
        "answer": "through"
    },
    {
        "question": "sólo",
        "answer": "just"
    },
    {
        "question": "forma",
        "answer": "form"
    },
    {
        "question": "frase",
        "answer": "sentence"
    },
    {
        "question": "gran",
        "answer": "great"
    },
    {
        "question": "pensar",
        "answer": "think"
    },
    {
        "question": "decir",
        "answer": "say"
    },
    {
        "question": "ayudar",
        "answer": "help"
    },
    {
        "question": "bajo",
        "answer": "low"
    },
    {
        "question": "línea",
        "answer": "line"
    },
    {
        "question": "ser distinto",
        "answer": "differ"
    },
    {
        "question": "a su vez,",
        "answer": "turn"
    },
    {
        "question": "causa",
        "answer": "cause"
    },
    {
        "question": "mucho",
        "answer": "much"
    },
    {
        "question": "significará",
        "answer": "mean"
    },
    {
        "question": "antes",
        "answer": "before"
    },
    {
        "question": "movimiento",
        "answer": "move"
    },
    {
        "question": "derecho",
        "answer": "right"
    },
    {
        "question": "niño",
        "answer": "boy"
    },
    {
        "question": "viejo",
        "answer": "old"
    },
    {
        "question": "demasiado",
        "answer": "too"
    },
    {
        "question": "misma",
        "answer": "same"
    },
    {
        "question": "ella",
        "answer": "she"
    },
    {
        "question": "todo",
        "answer": "all"
    },
    {
        "question": "hay",
        "answer": "there"
    },
    {
        "question": "cuando",
        "answer": "when"
    },
    {
        "question": "hasta",
        "answer": "up"
    },
    {
        "question": "uso",
        "answer": "use"
    },
    {
        "question": "su",
        "answer": "your"
    },
    {
        "question": "camino",
        "answer": "way"
    },
    {
        "question": "acerca",
        "answer": "about"
    },
    {
        "question": "muchos",
        "answer": "many"
    },
    {
        "question": "entonces",
        "answer": "then"
    },
    {
        "question": "ellos",
        "answer": "them"
    },
    {
        "question": "escribir",
        "answer": "write"
    },
    {
        "question": "haría",
        "answer": "would"
    },
    {
        "question": "como",
        "answer": "like"
    },
    {
        "question": "así",
        "answer": "so"
    },
    {
        "question": "éstos",
        "answer": "these"
    },
    {
        "question": "su",
        "answer": "her"
    },
    {
        "question": "largo",
        "answer": "long"
    },
    {
        "question": "hacer",
        "answer": "make"
    },
    {
        "question": "cosa",
        "answer": "thing"
    },
    {
        "question": "ver",
        "answer": "see"
    },
    {
        "question": "él",
        "answer": "him"
    },
    {
        "question": "dos",
        "answer": "two"
    },
    {
        "question": "tiene",
        "answer": "has"
    },
    {
        "question": "buscar",
        "answer": "look"
    },
    {
        "question": "más",
        "answer": "more"
    },
    {
        "question": "día",
        "answer": "day"
    },
    {
        "question": "podía",
        "answer": "could"
    },
    {
        "question": "ir",
        "answer": "go"
    },
    {
        "question": "venir",
        "answer": "come"
    },
    {
        "question": "hizo",
        "answer": "did"
    },
    {
        "question": "número",
        "answer": "number"
    },
    {
        "question": "sonar",
        "answer": "sound"
    },
    {
        "question": "no",
        "answer": "no"
    },
    {
        "question": "más",
        "answer": "most"
    },
    {
        "question": "personas",
        "answer": "people"
    },
    {
        "question": "mi",
        "answer": "my"
    },
    {
        "question": "sobre",
        "answer": "over"
    },
    {
        "question": "saber",
        "answer": "know"
    },
    {
        "question": "agua",
        "answer": "water"
    },
    {
        "question": "que",
        "answer": "than"
    },
    {
        "question": "llamada",
        "answer": "call"
    },
    {
        "question": "primero",
        "answer": "first"
    },
    {
        "question": "que",
        "answer": "who"
    },
    {
        "question": "puede",
        "answer": "may"
    },
    {
        "question": "abajo",
        "answer": "down"
    },
    {
        "question": "lado",
        "answer": "side"
    },
    {
        "question": "estado",
        "answer": "been"
    },
    {
        "question": "ahora",
        "answer": "now"
    },
    {
        "question": "encontrar",
        "answer": "find"
    },
    {
        "question": "cabeza",
        "answer": "head"
    },
    {
        "question": "de pie",
        "answer": "stand"
    },
    {
        "question": "propio",
        "answer": "own"
    },
    {
        "question": "página",
        "answer": "page"
    },
    {
        "question": "debería",
        "answer": "should"
    },
    {
        "question": "país",
        "answer": "country"
    },
    {
        "question": "encontrado",
        "answer": "found"
    },
    {
        "question": "respuesta",
        "answer": "answer"
    },
    {
        "question": "escuela",
        "answer": "school"
    },
    {
        "question": "crecer",
        "answer": "grow"
    },
    {
        "question": "estudio",
        "answer": "study"
    },
    {
        "question": "todavía",
        "answer": "still"
    },
    {
        "question": "aprender",
        "answer": "learn"
    },
    {
        "question": "planta",
        "answer": "plant"
    },
    {
        "question": "cubierta",
        "answer": "cover"
    },
    {
        "question": "alimentos",
        "answer": "food"
    },
    {
        "question": "sol",
        "answer": "sun"
    },
    {
        "question": "cuatro",
        "answer": "four"
    },
    {
        "question": "entre",
        "answer": "between"
    },
    {
        "question": "estado",
        "answer": "state"
    },
    {
        "question": "mantener",
        "answer": "keep"
    },
    {
        "question": "ojo",
        "answer": "eye"
    },
    {
        "question": "nunca",
        "answer": "never"
    },
    {
        "question": "último",
        "answer": "last"
    },
    {
        "question": "dejar",
        "answer": "let"
    },
    {
        "question": "pensado",
        "answer": "thought"
    },
    {
        "question": "ciudad",
        "answer": "city"
    },
    {
        "question": "árbol",
        "answer": "tree"
    },
    {
        "question": "cruzar",
        "answer": "cross"
    },
    {
        "question": "granja",
        "answer": "farm"
    },
    {
        "question": "duro",
        "answer": "hard"
    },
    {
        "question": "inicio",
        "answer": "start"
    },
    {
        "question": "podría",
        "answer": "might"
    },
    {
        "question": "historia",
        "answer": "story"
    },
    {
        "question": "sierra",
        "answer": "saw"
    },
    {
        "question": "ahora",
        "answer": "far"
    },
    {
        "question": "mar",
        "answer": "sea"
    },
    {
        "question": "dibujar",
        "answer": "draw"
    },
    {
        "question": "izquierda",
        "answer": "left"
    },
    {
        "question": "tarde",
        "answer": "late"
    },
    {
        "question": "ejecutar",
        "answer": "run"
    },
    {
        "question": "no",
        "answer": "don’t"
    },
    {
        "question": "mientras",
        "answer": "while"
    },
    {
        "question": "prensa",
        "answer": "press"
    },
    {
        "question": "Cerrar",
        "answer": "close"
    },
    {
        "question": "noche",
        "answer": "night"
    },
    {
        "question": "reales",
        "answer": "real"
    },
    {
        "question": "vida",
        "answer": "life"
    },
    {
        "question": "pocos",
        "answer": "few"
    },
    {
        "question": "norte",
        "answer": "north"
    },
    {
        "question": "libro",
        "answer": "book"
    },
    {
        "question": "llevar",
        "answer": "carry"
    },
    {
        "question": "tomó",
        "answer": "took"
    },
    {
        "question": "ciencia",
        "answer": "science"
    },
    {
        "question": "comer",
        "answer": "eat"
    },
    {
        "question": "habitación",
        "answer": "room"
    },
    {
        "question": "amigo",
        "answer": "friend"
    },
    {
        "question": "comenzó",
        "answer": "began"
    },
    {
        "question": "gusta",
        "answer": "idea"
    },
    {
        "question": "peces",
        "answer": "fish"
    },
    {
        "question": "montaña",
        "answer": "mountain"
    },
    {
        "question": "Deténgase",
        "answer": "stop"
    },
    {
        "question": "una vez",
        "answer": "once"
    },
    {
        "question": "base de",
        "answer": "base"
    },
    {
        "question": "escuchar",
        "answer": "hear"
    },
    {
        "question": "caballo",
        "answer": "horse"
    },
    {
        "question": "cortada",
        "answer": "cut"
    },
    {
        "question": "seguro",
        "answer": "sure"
    },
    {
        "question": "ver",
        "answer": "watch"
    },
    {
        "question": "colores",
        "answer": "color"
    },
    {
        "question": "cara",
        "answer": "face"
    },
    {
        "question": "madera",
        "answer": "wood"
    },
    {
        "question": "principal",
        "answer": "main"
    },
    {
        "question": "abierta",
        "answer": "open"
    },
    {
        "question": "parecer",
        "answer": "seem"
    },
    {
        "question": "juntos",
        "answer": "together"
    },
    {
        "question": "próximo",
        "answer": "next"
    },
    {
        "question": "blanco",
        "answer": "white"
    },
    {
        "question": "niños",
        "answer": "children"
    },
    {
        "question": "comenzar",
        "answer": "begin"
    },
    {
        "question": "conseguido",
        "answer": "got"
    },
    {
        "question": "caminar",
        "answer": "walk"
    },
    {
        "question": "ejemplo",
        "answer": "example"
    },
    {
        "question": "aliviar",
        "answer": "ease"
    },
    {
        "question": "papel",
        "answer": "paper"
    },
    {
        "question": "grupo",
        "answer": "group"
    },
    {
        "question": "siempre",
        "answer": "always"
    },
    {
        "question": "música",
        "answer": "music"
    },
    {
        "question": "los",
        "answer": "those"
    },
    {
        "question": "ambos",
        "answer": "both"
    },
    {
        "question": "marca",
        "answer": "mark"
    },
    {
        "question": "menudo",
        "answer": "often"
    },
    {
        "question": "carta",
        "answer": "letter"
    },
    {
        "question": "hasta",
        "answer": "until"
    },
    {
        "question": "milla",
        "answer": "mile"
    },
    {
        "question": "río",
        "answer": "river"
    },
    {
        "question": "coche",
        "answer": "car"
    },
    {
        "question": "pies",
        "answer": "feet"
    },
    {
        "question": "cuidado",
        "answer": "care"
    },
    {
        "question": "segundo",
        "answer": "second"
    },
    {
        "question": "suficiente",
        "answer": "enough"
    },
    {
        "question": "llano",
        "answer": "plain"
    },
    {
        "question": "chica",
        "answer": "girl"
    },
    {
        "question": "habitual",
        "answer": "usual"
    },
    {
        "question": "joven",
        "answer": "young"
    },
    {
        "question": "listo",
        "answer": "ready"
    },
    {
        "question": "por encima de",
        "answer": "above"
    },
    {
        "question": "nunca",
        "answer": "ever"
    },
    {
        "question": "rojo",
        "answer": "red"
    },
    {
        "question": "lista",
        "answer": "list"
    },
    {
        "question": "aunque",
        "answer": "though"
    },
    {
        "question": "sentir",
        "answer": "feel"
    },
    {
        "question": "charla",
        "answer": "talk"
    },
    {
        "question": "pájaro",
        "answer": "bird"
    },
    {
        "question": "pronto",
        "answer": "soon"
    },
    {
        "question": "cuerpo",
        "answer": "body"
    },
    {
        "question": "perro",
        "answer": "dog"
    },
    {
        "question": "familia",
        "answer": "family"
    },
    {
        "question": "directa",
        "answer": "direct"
    },
    {
        "question": "plantear",
        "answer": "pose"
    },
    {
        "question": "dejar",
        "answer": "leave"
    },
    {
        "question": "canción",
        "answer": "song"
    },
    {
        "question": "medir",
        "answer": "measure"
    },
    {
        "question": "puerta",
        "answer": "door"
    },
    {
        "question": "producto",
        "answer": "product"
    },
    {
        "question": "negro",
        "answer": "black"
    },
    {
        "question": "corto",
        "answer": "short"
    },
    {
        "question": "numeral",
        "answer": "numeral"
    },
    {
        "question": "clase",
        "answer": "class"
    },
    {
        "question": "viento",
        "answer": "wind"
    },
    {
        "question": "pregunta",
        "answer": "question"
    },
    {
        "question": "suceder",
        "answer": "happen"
    },
    {
        "question": "completo",
        "answer": "complete"
    },
    {
        "question": "buque",
        "answer": "ship"
    },
    {
        "question": "zona",
        "answer": "area"
    },
    {
        "question": "medio",
        "answer": "half"
    },
    {
        "question": "roca",
        "answer": "rock"
    },
    {
        "question": "orden",
        "answer": "order"
    },
    {
        "question": "fuego",
        "answer": "fire"
    },
    {
        "question": "sur",
        "answer": "south"
    },
    {
        "question": "problema",
        "answer": "problem"
    },
    {
        "question": "pieza",
        "answer": "piece"
    },
    {
        "question": "dicho",
        "answer": "told"
    },
    {
        "question": "sabía",
        "answer": "knew"
    },
    {
        "question": "pasar",
        "answer": "pass"
    },
    {
        "question": "desde",
        "answer": "since"
    },
    {
        "question": "cima",
        "answer": "top"
    },
    {
        "question": "todo",
        "answer": "whole"
    },
    {
        "question": "rey",
        "answer": "king"
    },
    {
        "question": "calle",
        "answer": "street"
    },
    {
        "question": "pulgadas",
        "answer": "inch"
    },
    {
        "question": "multiplicar",
        "answer": "multiply"
    },
    {
        "question": "nada",
        "answer": "nothing"
    },
    {
        "question": "curso",
        "answer": "course"
    },
    {
        "question": "quedarse",
        "answer": "stay"
    },
    {
        "question": "rueda",
        "answer": "wheel"
    },
    {
        "question": "completo",
        "answer": "full"
    },
    {
        "question": "fuerza",
        "answer": "force"
    },
    {
        "question": "azul",
        "answer": "blue"
    },
    {
        "question": "objeto",
        "answer": "object"
    },
    {
        "question": "decidir",
        "answer": "decide"
    },
    {
        "question": "superficie",
        "answer": "surface"
    },
    {
        "question": "profunda",
        "answer": "deep"
    },
    {
        "question": "luna",
        "answer": "moon"
    },
    {
        "question": "isla",
        "answer": "island"
    },
    {
        "question": "pie",
        "answer": "foot"
    },
    {
        "question": "sistema",
        "answer": "system"
    },
    {
        "question": "ocupado",
        "answer": "busy"
    },
    {
        "question": "prueba",
        "answer": "test"
    },
    {
        "question": "registro",
        "answer": "record"
    },
    {
        "question": "barco",
        "answer": "boat"
    },
    {
        "question": "común",
        "answer": "common"
    },
    {
        "question": "oro",
        "answer": "gold"
    },
    {
        "question": "posible",
        "answer": "possible"
    },
    {
        "question": "plano",
        "answer": "plane"
    },
    {
        "question": "lugar",
        "answer": "stead"
    },
    {
        "question": "seco",
        "answer": "dry"
    },
    {
        "question": "maravilla",
        "answer": "wonder"
    },
    {
        "question": "risa",
        "answer": "laugh"
    },
    {
        "question": "mil",
        "answer": "thousand"
    },
    {
        "question": "hace",
        "answer": "ago"
    },
    {
        "question": "corrió",
        "answer": "ran"
    },
    {
        "question": "comprobar",
        "answer": "check"
    },
    {
        "question": "juego",
        "answer": "game"
    },
    {
        "question": "forma",
        "answer": "shape"
    },
    {
        "question": "equiparar",
        "answer": "equate"
    },
    {
        "question": "caliente",
        "answer": "hot"
    },
    {
        "question": "señorita",
        "answer": "miss"
    },
    {
        "question": "traído",
        "answer": "brought"
    },
    {
        "question": "calor",
        "answer": "heat"
    },
    {
        "question": "nieve",
        "answer": "snow"
    },
    {
        "question": "neumáticos",
        "answer": "tire"
    },
    {
        "question": "traer",
        "answer": "bring"
    },
    {
        "question": "sí",
        "answer": "yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "distante",
        "answer": "distant"
    },
    {
        "question": "llenar",
        "answer": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "al este",
        "answer": "east"
    },
    {
        "question": "pintar",
        "answer": "paint"
    },
    {
        "question": "idioma",
        "answer": "language"
    },
    {
        "question": "entre",
        "answer": "among"
    },
    {
        "question": "unidad",
        "answer": "unit"
    },
    {
        "question": "potencia",
        "answer": "power"
    },
    {
        "question": "ciudad",
        "answer": "town"
    },
    {
        "question": "fina",
        "answer": "fine"
    },
    {
        "question": "cierto",
        "answer": "certain"
    },
    {
        "question": "volar",
        "answer": "fly"
    },
    {
        "question": "caer",
        "answer": "fall"
    },
    {
        "question": "conducir",
        "answer": "lead"
    },
    {
        "question": "grito",
        "answer": "cry"
    },
    {
        "question": "oscuro",
        "answer": "dark"
    },
    {
        "question": "máquina",
        "answer": "machine"
    },
    {
        "question": "nota",
        "answer": "note"
    },
    {
        "question": "espere",
        "answer": "wait"
    },
    {
        "question": "plan de",
        "answer": "plan"
    },
    {
        "question": "figura",
        "answer": "figure"
    },
    {
        "question": "estrella",
        "answer": "star"
    },
    {
        "question": "caja",
        "answer": "box"
    },
    {
        "question": "sustantivo",
        "answer": "noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "campo",
        "answer": "field"
    },
    {
        "question": "resto",
        "answer": "rest"
    },
    {
        "question": "correcta",
        "answer": "correct"
    },
    {
        "question": "capaz",
        "answer": "able"
    },
    {
        "question": "libra",
        "answer": "pound"
    },
    {
        "question": "hecho",
        "answer": "done"
    },
    {
        "question": "belleza",
        "answer": "beauty"
    },
    {
        "question": "unidad",
        "answer": "drive"
    },
    {
        "question": "destacado",
        "answer": "stood"
    },
    {
        "question": "contener",
        "answer": "contain"
    },
    {
        "question": "delante",
        "answer": "front"
    },
    {
        "question": "enseñar",
        "answer": "teach"
    },
    {
        "question": "semana",
        "answer": "week"
    },
    {
        "question": "último",
        "answer": "final"
    },
    {
        "question": "dio",
        "answer": "gave"
    },
    {
        "question": "verde",
        "answer": "green"
    },
    {
        "question": "oh",
        "answer": "oh"
    },
    {
        "question": "rápido",
        "answer": "quick"
    },
    {
        "question": "desarrollar",
        "answer": "develop"
    },
    {
        "question": "océano",
        "answer": "ocean"
    },
    {
        "question": "caliente",
        "answer": "warm"
    },
    {
        "question": "libre",
        "answer": "free"
    },
    {
        "question": "minuto",
        "answer": "minute"
    },
    {
        "question": "fuerte",
        "answer": "strong"
    },
    {
        "question": "especial",
        "answer": "special"
    },
    {
        "question": "mente",
        "answer": "mind"
    },
    {
        "question": "detrás",
        "answer": "behind"
    },
    {
        "question": "claro",
        "answer": "clear"
    },
    {
        "question": "cola",
        "answer": "tail"
    },
    {
        "question": "Produce",
        "answer": "produce"
    },
    {
        "question": "hecho",
        "answer": "fact"
    },
    {
        "question": "espacio",
        "answer": "space"
    },
    {
        "question": "oído",
        "answer": "heard"
    },
    {
        "question": "mejor",
        "answer": "best"
    },
    {
        "question": "horas",
        "answer": "hour"
    },
    {
        "question": "mejor",
        "answer": "better"
    },
    {
        "question": "verdadero",
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "durante",
        "answer": "during"
    },
    {
        "question": "cien",
        "answer": "hundred"
    },
    {
        "question": "cinco",
        "answer": "five"
    },
    {
        "question": "recordar",
        "answer": "remember"
    },
    {
        "question": "paso",
        "answer": "step"
    },
    {
        "question": "temprana",
        "answer": "early"
    },
    {
        "question": "mantenga",
        "answer": "hold"
    },
    {
        "question": "oeste",
        "answer": "west"
    },
    {
        "question": "suelo",
        "answer": "ground"
    },
    {
        "question": "interés",
        "answer": "interest"
    },
    {
        "question": "llegar",
        "answer": "reach"
    },
    {
        "question": "rápido",
        "answer": "fast"
    },
    {
        "question": "verbo",
        "answer": "verb"
    },
    {
        "question": "cantar",
        "answer": "sing"
    },
    {
        "question": "escuchar",
        "answer": "listen"
    },
    {
        "question": "seis",
        "answer": "six"
    },
    {
        "question": "mesa",
        "answer": "table"
    },
    {
        "question": "viajes",
        "answer": "travel"
    },
    {
        "question": "menos",
        "answer": "less"
    },
    {
        "question": "mañana",
        "answer": "morning"
    },
    {
        "question": "diez",
        "answer": "ten"
    },
    {
        "question": "sencilla",
        "answer": "simple"
    },
    {
        "question": "varios",
        "answer": "several"
    },
    {
        "question": "vocal",
        "answer": "vowel"
    },
    {
        "question": "hacia",
        "answer": "toward"
    },
    {
        "question": "guerra",
        "answer": "war"
    },
    {
        "question": "sentar",
        "answer": "lay"
    },
    {
        "question": "contra",
        "answer": "against"
    },
    {
        "question": "patrón",
        "answer": "pattern"
    },
    {
        "question": "lenta",
        "answer": "slow"
    },
    {
        "question": "centro",
        "answer": "center"
    },
    {
        "question": "amar",
        "answer": "love"
    },
    {
        "question": "persona",
        "answer": "person"
    },
    {
        "question": "dinero",
        "answer": "money"
    },
    {
        "question": "servir",
        "answer": "serve"
    },
    {
        "question": "aparecerá",
        "answer": "appear"
    },
    {
        "question": "carretera",
        "answer": "road"
    },
    {
        "question": "mapa",
        "answer": "map"
    },
    {
        "question": "lluvia",
        "answer": "rain"
    },
    {
        "question": "regla",
        "answer": "rule"
    },
    {
        "question": "gobernar",
        "answer": "govern"
    },
    {
        "question": "Halar",
        "answer": "pull"
    },
    {
        "question": "frío",
        "answer": "cold"
    },
    {
        "question": "aviso",
        "answer": "notice"
    },
    {
        "question": "voz",
        "answer": "voice"
    },
    {
        "question": "energía",
        "answer": "energy"
    },
    {
        "question": "caza",
        "answer": "hunt"
    },
    {
        "question": "probable",
        "answer": "probable"
    },
    {
        "question": "cama",
        "answer": "bed"
    },
    {
        "question": "hermano",
        "answer": "brother"
    },
    {
        "question": "huevo",
        "answer": "egg"
    },
    {
        "question": "paseo",
        "answer": "ride"
    },
    {
        "question": "celular",
        "answer": "cell"
    },
    {
        "question": "creer",
        "answer": "believe"
    },
    {
        "question": "quizás",
        "answer": "perhaps"
    },
    {
        "question": "recoger",
        "answer": "pick"
    },
    {
        "question": "repentina",
        "answer": "sudden"
    },
    {
        "question": "contar",
        "answer": "count"
    },
    {
        "question": "plaza",
        "answer": "square"
    },
    {
        "question": "razón",
        "answer": "reason"
    },
    {
        "question": "longitud",
        "answer": "length"
    },
    {
        "question": "representar",
        "answer": "represent"
    },
    {
        "question": "arte",
        "answer": "art"
    },
    {
        "question": "sujeto",
        "answer": "subject"
    },
    {
        "question": "región",
        "answer": "region"
    },
    {
        "question": "tamaño",
        "answer": "size"
    },
    {
        "question": "variar",
        "answer": "vary"
    },
    {
        "question": "resolver",
        "answer": "settle"
    },
    {
        "question": "hablar",
        "answer": "speak"
    },
    {
        "question": "peso",
        "answer": "weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "general",
        "answer": "general"
    },
    {
        "question": "hielo",
        "answer": "ice"
    },
    {
        "question": "materia",
        "answer": "matter"
    },
    {
        "question": "círculo",
        "answer": "circle"
    },
    {
        "question": "par",
        "answer": "pair"
    },
    {
        "question": "incluir",
        "answer": "include"
    },
    {
        "question": "brecha",
        "answer": "divide"
    },
    {
        "question": "sílaba",
        "answer": "syllable"
    },
    {
        "question": "sentido",
        "answer": "felt"
    },
    {
        "question": "gran",
        "answer": "grand"
    },
    {
        "question": "bola",
        "answer": "ball"
    },
    {
        "question": "aún",
        "answer": "yet"
    },
    {
        "question": "ola",
        "answer": "wave"
    },
    {
        "question": "caer",
        "answer": "drop"
    },
    {
        "question": "corazón",
        "answer": "heart"
    },
    {
        "question": "am",
        "answer": "am"
    },
    {
        "question": "presente",
        "answer": "present"
    },
    {
        "question": "pesada",
        "answer": "heavy"
    },
    {
        "question": "danza",
        "answer": "dance"
    },
    {
        "question": "motor",
        "answer": "engine"
    },
    {
        "question": "posición",
        "answer": "position"
    },
    {
        "question": "brazo",
        "answer": "arm"
    },
    {
        "question": "amplio",
        "answer": "wide"
    },
    {
        "question": "vela",
        "answer": "sail"
    },
    {
        "question": "materiales",
        "answer": "material"
    },
    {
        "question": "fracción",
        "answer": "fraction"
    },
    {
        "question": "bosque",
        "answer": "forest"
    },
    {
        "question": "sentarse",
        "answer": "sit"
    },
    {
        "question": "carrera",
        "answer": "race"
    },
    {
        "question": "ventana",
        "answer": "window"
    },
    {
        "question": "tienda",
        "answer": "store"
    },
    {
        "question": "verano",
        "answer": "summer"
    },
    {
        "question": "tren",
        "answer": "train"
    },
    {
        "question": "sueño",
        "answer": "sleep"
    },
    {
        "question": "demostrar",
        "answer": "prove"
    },
    {
        "question": "solitario",
        "answer": "lone"
    },
    {
        "question": "pierna",
        "answer": "leg"
    },
    {
        "question": "ejercicio",
        "answer": "exercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "pared",
        "answer": "wall"
    },
    {
        "question": "capturas",
        "answer": "catch"
    },
    {
        "question": "monte",
        "answer": "mount"
    },
    {
        "question": "desear",
        "answer": "wish"
    },
    {
        "question": "cielo",
        "answer": "sky"
    },
    {
        "question": "bordo",
        "answer": "board"
    },
    {
        "question": "alegría",
        "answer": "joy"
    },
    {
        "question": "invierno",
        "answer": "winter"
    },
    {
        "question": "satélite",
        "answer": "sat"
    },
    {
        "question": "escrito",
        "answer": "written"
    },
    {
        "question": "salvaje",
        "answer": "wild"
    },
    {
        "question": "instrumento",
        "answer": "instrument"
    },
    {
        "question": "guardado",
        "answer": "kept"
    },
    {
        "question": "vidrio",
        "answer": "glass"
    },
    {
        "question": "hierba",
        "answer": "grass"
    },
    {
        "question": "vaca",
        "answer": "cow"
    },
    {
        "question": "trabajo",
        "answer": "job"
    },
    {
        "question": "borde",
        "answer": "edge"
    },
    {
        "question": "signo",
        "answer": "sign"
    },
    {
        "question": "visita",
        "answer": "visit"
    },
    {
        "question": "pasado",
        "answer": "past"
    },
    {
        "question": "suave",
        "answer": "soft"
    },
    {
        "question": "diversión",
        "answer": "fun"
    },
    {
        "question": "brillante",
        "answer": "bright"
    },
    {
        "question": "gas",
        "answer": "gas"
    },
    {
        "question": "tiempo",
        "answer": "weather"
    },
    {
        "question": "mes",
        "answer": "month"
    },
    {
        "question": "millones",
        "answer": "million"
    },
    {
        "question": "soportar",
        "answer": "bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "acabado",
        "answer": "finish"
    },
    {
        "question": "feliz",
        "answer": "happy"
    },
    {
        "question": "esperanza",
        "answer": "hope"
    },
    {
        "question": "flor",
        "answer": "flower"
    },
    {
        "question": "vestir",
        "answer": "clothe"
    },
    {
        "question": "extraño",
        "answer": "strange"
    },
    {
        "question": "se ha ido",
        "answer": "gone"
    },
    {
        "question": "comercio",
        "answer": "trade"
    },
    {
        "question": "melodía",
        "answer": "melody"
    },
    {
        "question": "viaje",
        "answer": "trip"
    },
    {
        "question": "oficina",
        "answer": "office"
    },
    {
        "question": "recibir",
        "answer": "receive"
    },
    {
        "question": "fila",
        "answer": "row"
    },
    {
        "question": "boca",
        "answer": "mouth"
    },
    {
        "question": "exacta",
        "answer": "exact"
    },
    {
        "question": "símbolo",
        "answer": "symbol"
    },
    {
        "question": "morir",
        "answer": "die"
    },
    {
        "question": "menos",
        "answer": "least"
    },
    {
        "question": "problema",
        "answer": "trouble"
    },
    {
        "question": "grito",
        "answer": "shout"
    },
    {
        "question": "excepto",
        "answer": "except"
    },
    {
        "question": "escribió",
        "answer": "wrote"
    },
    {
        "question": "semilla",
        "answer": "seed"
    },
    {
        "question": "tono",
        "answer": "tone"
    },
    {
        "question": "unirse",
        "answer": "join"
    },
    {
        "question": "sugerir",
        "answer": "suggest"
    },
    {
        "question": "limpia",
        "answer": "clean"
    },
    {
        "question": "rotura",
        "answer": "break"
    },
    {
        "question": "dama",
        "answer": "lady"
    },
    {
        "question": "patio",
        "answer": "yard"
    },
    {
        "question": "aumentando",
        "answer": "rise"
    },
    {
        "question": "mal",
        "answer": "bad"
    },
    {
        "question": "golpe",
        "answer": "blow"
    },
    {
        "question": "aceite",
        "answer": "oil"
    },
    {
        "question": "sangre",
        "answer": "blood"
    },
    {
        "question": "tocar",
        "answer": "touch"
    },
    {
        "question": "creció",
        "answer": "grew"
    },
    {
        "question": "ciento",
        "answer": "cent"
    },
    {
        "question": "mezclar",
        "answer": "mix"
    },
    {
        "question": "equipo",
        "answer": "team"
    },
    {
        "question": "alambre",
        "answer": "wire"
    },
    {
        "question": "costo",
        "answer": "cost"
    },
    {
        "question": "perdido",
        "answer": "lost"
    },
    {
        "question": "marrón",
        "answer": "brown"
    },
    {
        "question": "desgaste",
        "answer": "wear"
    },
    {
        "question": "jardín",
        "answer": "garden"
    },
    {
        "question": "igual",
        "answer": "equal"
    },
    {
        "question": "enviado",
        "answer": "sent"
    },
    {
        "question": "elegir",
        "answer": "choose"
    },
    {
        "question": "cayó",
        "answer": "fell"
    },
    {
        "question": "encajar",
        "answer": "fit"
    },
    {
        "question": "fluir",
        "answer": "flow"
    },
    {
        "question": "justo",
        "answer": "fair"
    },
    {
        "question": "banco",
        "answer": "bank"
    },
    {
        "question": "recoger",
        "answer": "collect"
    },
    {
        "question": "guardar",
        "answer": "save"
    },
    {
        "question": "el control",
        "answer": "control"
    },
    {
        "question": "decimal",
        "answer": "decimal"
    },
    {
        "question": "oído",
        "answer": "ear"
    },
    {
        "question": "demás",
        "answer": "else"
    },
    {
        "question": "bastante",
        "answer": "quite"
    },
    {
        "question": "rompió",
        "answer": "broke"
    },
    {
        "question": "caso",
        "answer": "case"
    },
    {
        "question": "medio",
        "answer": "middle"
    },
    {
        "question": "matar",
        "answer": "kill"
    },
    {
        "question": "hijo",
        "answer": "son"
    },
    {
        "question": "lago",
        "answer": "lake"
    },
    {
        "question": "momento",
        "answer": "moment"
    },
    {
        "question": "escala",
        "answer": "scale"
    },
    {
        "question": "fuerte",
        "answer": "loud"
    },
    {
        "question": "primavera",
        "answer": "spring"
    },
    {
        "question": "observar",
        "answer": "observe"
    },
    {
        "question": "niño",
        "answer": "child"
    },
    {
        "question": "recta",
        "answer": "straight"
    },
    {
        "question": "consonante",
        "answer": "consonant"
    },
    {
        "question": "nación",
        "answer": "nation"
    },
    {
        "question": "diccionario",
        "answer": "dictionary"
    },
    {
        "question": "leche",
        "answer": "milk"
    },
    {
        "question": "velocidad",
        "answer": "speed"
    },
    {
        "question": "método",
        "answer": "method"
    },
    {
        "question": "órgano",
        "answer": "organ"
    },
    {
        "question": "pagar",
        "answer": "pay"
    },
    {
        "question": "edad",
        "answer": "age"
    },
    {
        "question": "sección",
        "answer": "section"
    },
    {
        "question": "vestido",
        "answer": "dress"
    },
    {
        "question": "nube",
        "answer": "cloud"
    },
    {
        "question": "sorpresa",
        "answer": "surprise"
    },
    {
        "question": "tranquila",
        "answer": "quiet"
    },
    {
        "question": "piedra",
        "answer": "stone"
    },
    {
        "question": "pequeño",
        "answer": "tiny"
    },
    {
        "question": "ascenso",
        "answer": "climb"
    },
    {
        "question": "fresco",
        "answer": "cool"
    },
    {
        "question": "diseño",
        "answer": "design"
    },
    {
        "question": "pobre",
        "answer": "poor"
    },
    {
        "question": "mucho",
        "answer": "lot"
    },
    {
        "question": "experimento",
        "answer": "experiment"
    },
    {
        "question": "inferior",
        "answer": "bottom"
    },
    {
        "question": "clave",
        "answer": "key"
    },
    {
        "question": "hierro",
        "answer": "iron"
    },
    {
        "question": "sola",
        "answer": "single"
    },
    {
        "question": "palillo",
        "answer": "stick"
    },
    {
        "question": "plana",
        "answer": "flat"
    },
    {
        "question": "veinte",
        "answer": "twenty"
    },
    {
        "question": "piel",
        "answer": "skin"
    },
    {
        "question": "sonrisa",
        "answer": "smile"
    },
    {
        "question": "pliegue",
        "answer": "crease"
    },
    {
        "question": "agujero",
        "answer": "hole"
    },
    {
        "question": "saltar",
        "answer": "jump"
    },
    {
        "question": "bebé",
        "answer": "baby"
    },
    {
        "question": "ocho",
        "answer": "eight"
    },
    {
        "question": "pueblo",
        "answer": "village"
    },
    {
        "question": "se reúnen",
        "answer": "meet"
    },
    {
        "question": "raíz",
        "answer": "root"
    },
    {
        "question": "comprar",
        "answer": "buy"
    },
    {
        "question": "aumentar",
        "answer": "raise"
    },
    {
        "question": "resolver",
        "answer": "solve"
    },
    {
        "question": "de metal",
        "answer": "metal"
    },
    {
        "question": "si",
        "answer": "whether"
    },
    {
        "question": "empujar",
        "answer": "push"
    },
    {
        "question": "siete",
        "answer": "seven"
    },
    {
        "question": "párrafo",
        "answer": "paragraph"
    },
    {
        "question": "tercero",
        "answer": "third"
    },
    {
        "question": "deberá",
        "answer": "shall"
    },
    {
        "question": "en espera",
        "answer": "held"
    },
    {
        "question": "pelo",
        "answer": "hair"
    },
    {
        "question": "describir",
        "answer": "describe"
    },
    {
        "question": "cocinero",
        "answer": "cook"
    },
    {
        "question": "piso",
        "answer": "floor"
    },
    {
        "question": "ya sea",
        "answer": "either"
    },
    {
        "question": "resultado",
        "answer": "result"
    },
    {
        "question": "quemar",
        "answer": "burn"
    },
    {
        "question": "colina",
        "answer": "hill"
    },
    {
        "question": "seguro",
        "answer": "safe"
    },
    {
        "question": "gato",
        "answer": "cat"
    },
    {
        "question": "siglo",
        "answer": "century"
    },
    {
        "question": "considerar",
        "answer": "consider"
    },
    {
        "question": "tipo",
        "answer": "type"
    },
    {
        "question": "ley",
        "answer": "law"
    },
    {
        "question": "bit",
        "answer": "bit"
    },
    {
        "question": "costa",
        "answer": "coast"
    },
    {
        "question": "copia",
        "answer": "copy"
    },
    {
        "question": "frase",
        "answer": "phrase"
    },
    {
        "question": "silencio",
        "answer": "silent"
    },
    {
        "question": "de altura",
        "answer": "tall"
    },
    {
        "question": "arena",
        "answer": "sand"
    },
    {
        "question": "suelo",
        "answer": "soil"
    },
    {
        "question": "rollo",
        "answer": "roll"
    },
    {
        "question": "temperatura",
        "answer": "temperature"
    },
    {
        "question": "dedo",
        "answer": "finger"
    },
    {
        "question": "industria",
        "answer": "industry"
    },
    {
        "question": "valor",
        "answer": "value"
    },
    {
        "question": "lucha",
        "answer": "fight"
    },
    {
        "question": "mentira",
        "answer": "lie"
    },
    {
        "question": "batir",
        "answer": "beat"
    },
    {
        "question": "excitar",
        "answer": "excite"
    },
    {
        "question": "naturales",
        "answer": "natural"
    },
    {
        "question": "vista",
        "answer": "view"
    },
    {
        "question": "sentido",
        "answer": "sense"
    },
    {
        "question": "de capital",
        "answer": "capital"
    },
    {
        "question": "no lo hará",
        "answer": "won’t"
    },
    {
        "question": "silla",
        "answer": "chair"
    },
    {
        "question": "peligro",
        "answer": "danger"
    },
    {
        "question": "fruta",
        "answer": "fruit"
    },
    {
        "question": "rica",
        "answer": "rich"
    },
    {
        "question": "de espesor",
        "answer": "thick"
    },
    {
        "question": "soldado",
        "answer": "soldier"
    },
    {
        "question": "proceso",
        "answer": "process"
    },
    {
        "question": "operar",
        "answer": "operate"
    },
    {
        "question": "práctica",
        "answer": "practice"
    },
    {
        "question": "separada",
        "answer": "separate"
    },
    {
        "question": "difícil",
        "answer": "difficult"
    },
    {
        "question": "médico",
        "answer": "doctor"
    },
    {
        "question": "por favor",
        "answer": "please"
    },
    {
        "question": "proteger",
        "answer": "protect"
    },
    {
        "question": "mediodía",
        "answer": "noon"
    },
    {
        "question": "de cultivos",
        "answer": "crop"
    },
    {
        "question": "moderno",
        "answer": "modern"
    },
    {
        "question": "elemento",
        "answer": "element"
    },
    {
        "question": "golpear",
        "answer": "hit"
    },
    {
        "question": "estudiante",
        "answer": "student"
    },
    {
        "question": "esquina",
        "answer": "corner"
    },
    {
        "question": "partido",
        "answer": "party"
    },
    {
        "question": "suministro",
        "answer": "supply"
    },
    {
        "question": "cuya",
        "answer": "whose"
    },
    {
        "question": "localizar",
        "answer": "locate"
    },
    {
        "question": "anillo",
        "answer": "ring"
    },
    {
        "question": "carácter",
        "answer": "character"
    },
    {
        "question": "insecto",
        "answer": "insect"
    },
    {
        "question": "capturado",
        "answer": "caught"
    },
    {
        "question": "período",
        "answer": "period"
    },
    {
        "question": "indicar",
        "answer": "indicate"
    },
    {
        "question": "Radio",
        "answer": "radio"
    },
    {
        "question": "habló",
        "answer": "spoke"
    },
    {
        "question": "átomo",
        "answer": "atom"
    },
    {
        "question": "humana",
        "answer": "human"
    },
    {
        "question": "historia",
        "answer": "history"
    },
    {
        "question": "efecto",
        "answer": "effect"
    },
    {
        "question": "eléctrica",
        "answer": "electric"
    },
    {
        "question": "esperar",
        "answer": "expect"
    },
    {
        "question": "hueso",
        "answer": "bone"
    },
    {
        "question": "ferrocarril",
        "answer": "rail"
    },
    {
        "question": "imaginar",
        "answer": "imagine"
    },
    {
        "question": "proporcionar",
        "answer": "provide"
    },
    {
        "question": "acuerdo",
        "answer": "agree"
    },
    {
        "question": "por tanto,",
        "answer": "thus"
    },
    {
        "question": "suave",
        "answer": "gentle"
    },
    {
        "question": "mujer",
        "answer": "woman"
    },
    {
        "question": "capitán",
        "answer": "captain"
    },
    {
        "question": "adivinar",
        "answer": "guess"
    },
    {
        "question": "necesario",
        "answer": "necessary"
    },
    {
        "question": "agudo",
        "answer": "sharp"
    },
    {
        "question": "ala",
        "answer": "wing"
    },
    {
        "question": "crear",
        "answer": "create"
    },
    {
        "question": "vecino",
        "answer": "neighbor"
    },
    {
        "question": "lavado",
        "answer": "wash"
    },
    {
        "question": "bate",
        "answer": "bat"
    },
    {
        "question": "más bien",
        "answer": "rather"
    },
    {
        "question": "multitud",
        "answer": "crowd"
    },
    {
        "question": "maíz",
        "answer": "corn"
    },
    {
        "question": "comparar",
        "answer": "compare"
    },
    {
        "question": "poema",
        "answer": "poem"
    },
    {
        "question": "cadena",
        "answer": "string"
    },
    {
        "question": "campana",
        "answer": "bell"
    },
    {
        "question": "dependerá",
        "answer": "depend"
    },
    {
        "question": "carne",
        "answer": "meat"
    },
    {
        "question": "frotar",
        "answer": "rub"
    },
    {
        "question": "tubo",
        "answer": "tube"
    },
    {
        "question": "famoso",
        "answer": "famous"
    },
    {
        "question": "dólar",
        "answer": "dollar"
    },
    {
        "question": "corriente",
        "answer": "stream"
    },
    {
        "question": "miedo",
        "answer": "fear"
    },
    {
        "question": "vista",
        "answer": "sight"
    },
    {
        "question": "delgado",
        "answer": "thin"
    },
    {
        "question": "triángulo",
        "answer": "triangle"
    },
    {
        "question": "planeta",
        "answer": "planet"
    },
    {
        "question": "prisa",
        "answer": "hurry"
    },
    {
        "question": "jefe",
        "answer": "chief"
    },
    {
        "question": "colonia",
        "answer": "colony"
    },
    {
        "question": "reloj",
        "answer": "clock"
    },
    {
        "question": "mina",
        "answer": "mine"
    },
    {
        "question": "empate",
        "answer": "tie"
    },
    {
        "question": "entrar",
        "answer": "enter"
    },
    {
        "question": "importante",
        "answer": "major"
    },
    {
        "question": "fresco",
        "answer": "fresh"
    },
    {
        "question": "búsqueda",
        "answer": "search"
    },
    {
        "question": "enviar",
        "answer": "send"
    },
    {
        "question": "amarillo",
        "answer": "yellow"
    },
    {
        "question": "pistola",
        "answer": "gun"
    },
    {
        "question": "permitir",
        "answer": "allow"
    },
    {
        "question": "print",
        "answer": "print"
    },
    {
        "question": "muerto",
        "answer": "dead"
    },
    {
        "question": "lugar",
        "answer": "spot"
    },
    {
        "question": "desierto",
        "answer": "desert"
    },
    {
        "question": "traje",
        "answer": "suit"
    },
    {
        "question": "actual",
        "answer": "current"
    },
    {
        "question": "ascensor",
        "answer": "lift"
    },
    {
        "question": "rosa",
        "answer": "rose"
    },
    {
        "question": "llegar",
        "answer": "arrive"
    },
    {
        "question": "master",
        "answer": "master"
    },
    {
        "question": "pista",
        "answer": "track"
    },
    {
        "question": "padre",
        "answer": "parent"
    },
    {
        "question": "orilla",
        "answer": "shore"
    },
    {
        "question": "división",
        "answer": "division"
    },
    {
        "question": "hoja",
        "answer": "sheet"
    },
    {
        "question": "sustancia",
        "answer": "substance"
    },
    {
        "question": "favorecer",
        "answer": "favor"
    },
    {
        "question": "conectar",
        "answer": "connect"
    },
    {
        "question": "mensaje",
        "answer": "post"
    },
    {
        "question": "pasar",
        "answer": "spend"
    },
    {
        "question": "acorde",
        "answer": "chord"
    },
    {
        "question": "grasa",
        "answer": "fat"
    },
    {
        "question": "contento",
        "answer": "glad"
    },
    {
        "question": "originales",
        "answer": "original"
    },
    {
        "question": "cuota",
        "answer": "share"
    },
    {
        "question": "estación",
        "answer": "station"
    },
    {
        "question": "papá",
        "answer": "dad"
    },
    {
        "question": "pan",
        "answer": "bread"
    },
    {
        "question": "cobrar",
        "answer": "charge"
    },
    {
        "question": "adecuada",
        "answer": "proper"
    },
    {
        "question": "barra",
        "answer": "bar"
    },
    {
        "question": "oferta",
        "answer": "offer"
    },
    {
        "question": "segmento",
        "answer": "segment"
    },
    {
        "question": "esclavo",
        "answer": "slave"
    },
    {
        "question": "pato",
        "answer": "duck"
    },
    {
        "question": "instantánea",
        "answer": "instant"
    },
    {
        "question": "mercado",
        "answer": "market"
    },
    {
        "question": "grado",
        "answer": "degree"
    },
    {
        "question": "poblar",
        "answer": "populate"
    },
    {
        "question": "polluelo",
        "answer": "chick"
    },
    {
        "question": "querido",
        "answer": "dear"
    },
    {
        "question": "enemigo",
        "answer": "enemy"
    },
    {
        "question": "responder",
        "answer": "reply"
    },
    {
        "question": "bebida",
        "answer": "drink"
    },
    {
        "question": "producirse",
        "answer": "occur"
    },
    {
        "question": "apoyo",
        "answer": "support"
    },
    {
        "question": "discurso",
        "answer": "speech"
    },
    {
        "question": "naturaleza",
        "answer": "nature"
    },
    {
        "question": "alcance",
        "answer": "range"
    },
    {
        "question": "vapor",
        "answer": "steam"
    },
    {
        "question": "movimiento",
        "answer": "motion"
    },
    {
        "question": "camino",
        "answer": "path"
    },
    {
        "question": "líquido",
        "answer": "liquid"
    },
    {
        "question": "log",
        "answer": "log"
    },
    {
        "question": "significado",
        "answer": "meant"
    },
    {
        "question": "cociente",
        "answer": "quotient"
    },
    {
        "question": "dientes",
        "answer": "teeth"
    },
    {
        "question": "concha",
        "answer": "shell"
    },
    {
        "question": "cuello",
        "answer": "neck"
    },
    {
        "question": "oxígeno",
        "answer": "oxygen"
    },
    {
        "question": "azúcar",
        "answer": "sugar"
    },
    {
        "question": "muerte",
        "answer": "death"
    },
    {
        "question": "bastante",
        "answer": "pretty"
    },
    {
        "question": "habilidad",
        "answer": "skill"
    },
    {
        "question": "mujeres",
        "answer": "women"
    },
    {
        "question": "temporada",
        "answer": "season"
    },
    {
        "question": "solución",
        "answer": "solution"
    },
    {
        "question": "imán",
        "answer": "magnet"
    },
    {
        "question": "plata",
        "answer": "silver"
    },
    {
        "question": "gracias",
        "answer": "thank"
    },
    {
        "question": "rama",
        "answer": "branch"
    },
    {
        "question": "partido",
        "answer": "match"
    },
    {
        "question": "sufijo",
        "answer": "suffix"
    },
    {
        "question": "especialmente",
        "answer": "especially"
    },
    {
        "question": "higo",
        "answer": "fig"
    },
    {
        "question": "miedo",
        "answer": "afraid"
    },
    {
        "question": "enorme",
        "answer": "huge"
    },
    {
        "question": "hermana",
        "answer": "sister"
    },
    {
        "question": "acero",
        "answer": "steel"
    },
    {
        "question": "discutir",
        "answer": "discuss"
    },
    {
        "question": "adelante",
        "answer": "forward"
    },
    {
        "question": "similar",
        "answer": "similar"
    },
    {
        "question": "guiar",
        "answer": "guide"
    },
    {
        "question": "experiencia",
        "answer": "experience"
    },
    {
        "question": "puntuación",
        "answer": "score"
    },
    {
        "question": "manzana",
        "answer": "apple"
    },
    {
        "question": "comprado",
        "answer": "bought"
    },
    {
        "question": "llevado",
        "answer": "led"
    },
    {
        "question": "pitch",
        "answer": "pitch"
    },
    {
        "question": "abrigo",
        "answer": "coat"
    },
    {
        "question": "masa",
        "answer": "mass"
    },
    {
        "question": "tarjeta",
        "answer": "card"
    },
    {
        "question": "banda",
        "answer": "band"
    },
    {
        "question": "cuerda",
        "answer": "rope"
    },
    {
        "question": "deslizamiento",
        "answer": "slip"
    },
    {
        "question": "ganar",
        "answer": "win"
    },
    {
        "question": "soñar",
        "answer": "dream"
    },
    {
        "question": "noche",
        "answer": "evening"
    },
    {
        "question": "condición",
        "answer": "condition"
    },
    {
        "question": "pienso",
        "answer": "feed"
    },
    {
        "question": "herramienta",
        "answer": "tool"
    },
    {
        "question": "totales",
        "answer": "total"
    },
    {
        "question": "básico",
        "answer": "basic"
    },
    {
        "question": "olor",
        "answer": "smell"
    },
    {
        "question": "valle",
        "answer": "valley"
    },
    {
        "question": "ni",
        "answer": "nor"
    },
    {
        "question": "doble",
        "answer": "double"
    },
    {
        "question": "asiento",
        "answer": "seat"
    },
    {
        "question": "continuar",
        "answer": "continue"
    },
    {
        "question": "bloque",
        "answer": "block"
    },
    {
        "question": "tabla",
        "answer": "chart"
    },
    {
        "question": "sombrero",
        "answer": "hat"
    },
    {
        "question": "vender",
        "answer": "sell"
    },
    {
        "question": "éxito",
        "answer": "success"
    },
    {
        "question": "empresa",
        "answer": "company"
    },
    {
        "question": "restar",
        "answer": "subtract"
    },
    {
        "question": "evento",
        "answer": "event"
    },
    {
        "question": "particular,",
        "answer": "particular"
    },
    {
        "question": "acuerdo",
        "answer": "deal"
    },
    {
        "question": "nadar",
        "answer": "swim"
    },
    {
        "question": "plazo",
        "answer": "term"
    },
    {
        "question": "opuesta",
        "answer": "opposite"
    },
    {
        "question": "esposa",
        "answer": "wife"
    },
    {
        "question": "zapato",
        "answer": "shoe"
    },
    {
        "question": "hombro",
        "answer": "shoulder"
    },
    {
        "question": "propagación",
        "answer": "spread"
    },
    {
        "question": "organizar",
        "answer": "arrange"
    },
    {
        "question": "campamento",
        "answer": "camp"
    },
    {
        "question": "inventar",
        "answer": "invent"
    },
    {
        "question": "algodón",
        "answer": "cotton"
    },
    {
        "question": "nacido",
        "answer": "born"
    },
    {
        "question": "determinar",
        "answer": "determine"
    },
    {
        "question": "cuarto de galón",
        "answer": "quart"
    },
    {
        "question": "nueve",
        "answer": "nine"
    },
    {
        "question": "camión",
        "answer": "truck"
    },
    {
        "question": "ruido",
        "answer": "noise"
    },
    {
        "question": "nivel",
        "answer": "level"
    },
    {
        "question": "oportunidad",
        "answer": "chance"
    },
    {
        "question": "reunir",
        "answer": "gather"
    },
    {
        "question": "tienda",
        "answer": "shop"
    },
    {
        "question": "tramo",
        "answer": "stretch"
    },
    {
        "question": "lanzar",
        "answer": "throw"
    },
    {
        "question": "brillo",
        "answer": "shine"
    },
    {
        "question": "propiedad",
        "answer": "property"
    },
    {
        "question": "columna",
        "answer": "column"
    },
    {
        "question": "molécula",
        "answer": "molecule"
    },
    {
        "question": "seleccionar",
        "answer": "select"
    },
    {
        "question": "mal",
        "answer": "wrong"
    },
    {
        "question": "gris",
        "answer": "gray"
    },
    {
        "question": "repita",
        "answer": "repeat"
    },
    {
        "question": "exigir",
        "answer": "require"
    },
    {
        "question": "amplio",
        "answer": "broad"
    },
    {
        "question": "preparar",
        "answer": "prepare"
    },
    {
        "question": "sal",
        "answer": "salt"
    },
    {
        "question": "nariz",
        "answer": "nose"
    },
    {
        "question": "plurales",
        "answer": "plural"
    },
    {
        "question": "cólera",
        "answer": "anger"
    },
    {
        "question": "reclamación",
        "answer": "claim"
    },
    {
        "question": "continente",
        "answer": "continent"
    }
]